[
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:1, wherein do ye stand?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:1",
        "answer": "in the gospel (which I preached unto you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:1, what do I declare unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:1",
        "answer": "the gospel (which I preached unto you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:2, how keep what I have preached unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:2",
        "answer": "in memory"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:3, how did Christ die for our sins?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "according to the scriptures"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:3.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "For I delivered unto you first of all that which I also received, how that Christ died for our sins according to the scriptures;"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:3, when did I deliver unto you that which I also received?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "first (of all)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:4, when did he rise again?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "the third day"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was buried in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "(he) Christ (v. 3)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And that he was buried, and that he rose again.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "the third day according to the scriptures"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:5, of whom was he seen?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:5",
        "answer": "of Cephas, then of the twelve"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many brethren saw Christ at once in 1 Corinthians 15 after his resurrection?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:6",
        "answer": "above five hundred brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who remain unto this present in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:6",
        "answer": "the greater part (of the above 500 brethren who saw the resurrected Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:7, of whom was he seen after that?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:7",
        "answer": "of James; then of all the apostles."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:8, when was he seen of Paul?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:8",
        "answer": "last of all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:9, why am I not meet to be called an apostle?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:9",
        "answer": "because I persecuted the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:9, what am I?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:9",
        "answer": "the least of the apostles"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:10, by what am I what I am?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:10, what was not in vain?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "his grace which was bestowed upon me"
    },
    {
        "question": "How in 1 Corinthians 15 did I labour?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "more abundantly than they all"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But by the grace of God I am what I am: and his grace which was bestowed upon me was not in vain; but I laboured more abundantly than they all: yet not I, but the grace of God which was with me.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 15:10"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:12, how is Christ preached?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:12",
        "answer": "that he rose from the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:13, who is not risen, if there be no resurrection of the dead?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:13",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:14, what two are vain if Christ be not risen?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:14",
        "answer": "our preaching and your faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:15, what are we found?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:15",
        "answer": "false witnesses (of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:17, what is your faith?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "vain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:17.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "And if Christ be not raised, your faith is vain; ye are yet in your sins."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:17, where are ye yet?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "in your sins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are perished in 1 Corinthians 15, if Christ be not raised?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:18",
        "answer": "they also which are fallen asleep in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 15 which uses the word: miserable",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:19",
        "answer": "If in this life only we have hope in Christ, we are of all men most miserable."
    },
    {
        "question": "When are we the most miserable of all men in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:19",
        "answer": "If in this life only we have hope in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:20, when is Christ risen from the dead?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:20",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:20, what is Christ become?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:20",
        "answer": "the firstfruits of them that slept"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:21, what two came by man?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:21",
        "answer": "death and the resurrection of the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:21, by whom came the resurrection of the dead?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:21",
        "answer": "man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where shall all be made alive in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:22",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:22, where do all die?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:22",
        "answer": "in Adam"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:23, when does every man come?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:23",
        "answer": "in his own order"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:23, what is Christ?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:23",
        "answer": "the firstfruits"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what cometh?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:24",
        "answer": "the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what three shall he have put down?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:24",
        "answer": "all rule and all authority and power"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what shall he have delivered up to God?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "10 15:24",
        "answer": "the kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where will Christ put all enemies in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:25",
        "answer": "under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:25, when must he reign?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:25",
        "answer": "till he hath put all enemies under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last enemy in 1 Corinthians 15 that shall be destroyed?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:26",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is excepted in 1 Corinthians 15 when he saith all things are put under him?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:27",
        "answer": "he which did put all things under him (God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:27, where hath he put all things?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:27",
        "answer": "under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall be subdued unto him in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:28",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:28, unto whom shall the Son also himself be subject?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:28",
        "answer": "him that put all things under him (God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "When do we stand in jeopardy in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:30",
        "answer": "every hour"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:31, what do I have in Christ Jesus our Lord?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:31",
        "answer": "your rejoicing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:31, when do I die?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:31",
        "answer": "daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where had Paul fought with beasts in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:32",
        "answer": "at Ephesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:32, when do we die?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:32",
        "answer": "to morrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "What corrupt good manners in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:33",
        "answer": "evil communications"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Be not deceived.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:33",
        "answer": "evil communications corrupt good manners"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:34, what do some not have?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "the knowledge of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:34, how do I speak this?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "to your shame"
    },
    {
        "question": "How awake in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "to righteousness (and sin not)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:36, what is not quickened, except it die?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:36",
        "answer": "that which thou sowest"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:36, except what, that which thou sowest is not quickened?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:36",
        "answer": "except it die"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:37, what sowest thou?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:37",
        "answer": "bare grain (it may chance of wheat, or of some other grain)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:38, who giveth it a body?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:38",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:38, how does God give it a body?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:38",
        "answer": "as it hath pleased him (and to every seed his own body)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:39, what is not the same flesh?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:39",
        "answer": "All flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:39, what are four kinds of flesh?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:39",
        "answer": "one kind of flesh of men, another flesh of beasts, another of fishes, and another of birds"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:40, what are two kinds of bodies?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:40",
        "answer": "celestial bodies, and bodies terrestrial"
    },
    {
        "question": "What differeth from another in glory in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:41",
        "answer": "(one) star"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:41, what are three glories?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:41",
        "answer": "one glory of the sun, and another glory of the moon, and another glory of the stars"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:42, how is it raised?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:42",
        "answer": "in incorruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:42, how is it sown?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:42",
        "answer": "in corruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:43, in what two is it sown?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:43",
        "answer": "in dishonour and in weakness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:44, what is it sown?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:44",
        "answer": "a natural body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:44, what is it raised?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:44",
        "answer": "a spiritual body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:45, what was the first Adam made?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:45",
        "answer": "a living soul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was made a quickening spirit in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:45",
        "answer": "the last Adam"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:46, what was first?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:46",
        "answer": "that which is natural"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:47, who is of the earth?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:47",
        "answer": "The first man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:47, who is the Lord from heaven?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:47",
        "answer": "the second man"
    },
    {
        "question": "What have we borne in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:49",
        "answer": "the image of the earthy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:50, what cannot inherit the kingdom of God?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:50",
        "answer": "flesh and blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:51, what do I show you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:51",
        "answer": "a mystery"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:51, what shall we all be?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:51",
        "answer": "changed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:52, what shall sound?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:52",
        "answer": "the trumpet"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:52, how shall the dead be raised?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:52",
        "answer": "incorruptible"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:53, what must this corruptible do?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:53",
        "answer": "put on incorruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:53, what must put on immortality?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:53",
        "answer": "this mortal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is swallowed up in victory in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:54",
        "answer": "Death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: O death, where is thy sting? O grave, where is thy victory?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:55",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 15:55"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:56, what is the strength of sin?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:56",
        "answer": "the law"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sting of death in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:56",
        "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:57.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "But thanks be to God, which giveth us the victory through our Lord Jesus Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:57, what does God give us?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "the victory (through our Lord Jesus Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:57, what be to God?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 15 which uses the word: unmoveable",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "Therefore, my beloved brethren, be ye stedfast, unmoveable, always abounding in the work of the Lord, forasmuch as ye know that your labour is not in vain in the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "Why be stedfast and unmoveable in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "forasmuch as ye know that your labour is not in vain in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:58, when abound in the work of the Lord?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "For whom is the collection in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:1",
        "answer": "the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:1, to whom have I given order?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:1",
        "answer": "to the churches of Galatia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: prospered",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "Upon the first day of the week let every one of you lay by him in store, as God hath prospered him, that there be no gatherings when I come."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, when let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "Upon the first day of the week"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, how let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "as God hath prospered him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, why let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "that there be no gatherings when I come"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom will I send to bring your liberality unto Jerusalem in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "whomsoever ye shall approve (by your letters)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:3, when will I send them?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "when I come"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:3, where will I send them?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "unto Jerusalem"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:4, if what, they shall go with me?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:4",
        "answer": "if it be meet that I go also"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:5, where do I pass?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:5",
        "answer": "through Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:5, when will I now come unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:5",
        "answer": "when I shall pass through Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:6, where will I winter?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:6",
        "answer": "with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:6, where may ye bring me?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:6",
        "answer": "on my journey (whithersoever I go)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:7, how long do I trust to tarry with you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:7",
        "answer": "a while"
    },
    {
        "question": "When will I tarry at Ephesus in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:8",
        "answer": "until Pentecost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Until Pentecost, where will I tarry in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:8",
        "answer": "at Ephesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For a great door and effectual is opened unto me.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "and there are many adversaries"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is opened unto me in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "a great door and effectual"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:9, what are many?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "many adversaries"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Now if Timotheus come, see that he may be with you without fear: for he worketh the work of the Lord, as I also do.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 16:10"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:10, how see that Timotheus may be with you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "without fear"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:10, who worketh the work of the Lord?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "(he) Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom conduct forth in peace in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "(him) Timotheus (v. 10)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 16:11.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "Let no man therefore despise him: but conduct him forth in peace, that he may come unto me: for I look for him with the brethren."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:11, let who despise him?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom did I greatly desire to come unto you with the brethren in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:12",
        "answer": "(him) Apollos"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:12, when will Apollos come?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:12",
        "answer": "when he shall have convenient time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where stand fast in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "in the faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "How quit you in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "like men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: quit",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "Watch ye, stand fast in the faith, quit you like men, be strong."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:13, be what?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "strong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Let all your things be done with charity.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:14",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 16:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:14, how let all your things be done?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:14",
        "answer": "with charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:15, what is the firstfruits of Achaia?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:15",
        "answer": "(it) the house of Stephanas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who have addicted themselves to the ministry of the saints in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:15",
        "answer": "the house of Stephanas"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:16, where submit yourselves?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:16",
        "answer": "unto such (the house of Stephanas), and to every one that helpeth with us, and laboureth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:17, of what am I glad?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "of the coming of Stephanas and Fortunatus and Achaicus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"I am glad of the coming of Stephanas and Fortunatus.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "and Achaicus: for that which was lacking on your part they have supplied"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:17, what have they supplied?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "that which was lacking on your part"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:18, what have they refreshed?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:18",
        "answer": "my spirit and yours"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 1 Corinthians 16 salute you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:19",
        "answer": "The churches of Asia, Aquila and Priscilla, with the church that is in their house."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:19, what is in the house of Aquila and Priscilla?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:19",
        "answer": "the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:20, who greet you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:20",
        "answer": "All the brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:20, how greet ye one another?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:20",
        "answer": "with an holy kiss"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose salutation was with his own hand in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:21",
        "answer": "The salutation of me Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Let who be Anathema Maranatha in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:22",
        "answer": "If any man love not the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: Maranatha",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:22",
        "answer": "If any man love not the Lord Jesus Christ, let him be Anathema Maranatha."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:23, what be with you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:23",
        "answer": "The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 16:23.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:23",
        "answer": "The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ be with you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:24, what be with you all?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:24",
        "answer": "My love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:24, in whom, my love be with you all?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "1C 16:24",
        "answer": "in Christ Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, what is Paul?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "an apostle of Jesus Christ (by the will of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, what is at Corinth?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Timothy in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "our brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, who are in all Achaia?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "(all the) saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Grace be to you and peace from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:2"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:2, from whom is grace and peace?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:2, what be to you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "Grace and peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Blessed be God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 1 be blessed?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "God (even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:3, what are three titles of God?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, whom may we be able to comfort?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "them which are in any trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 1:4.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "Who comforteth us in all our tribulation, that we may be able to comfort them which are in any trouble, by the comfort wherewith we ourselves are comforted of God."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, in what does God comfort us?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "in all our tribulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, by what may we be able to comfort them that are in any trouble?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "the comfort wherewith we ourselves are comforted of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: aboundeth",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "For as the sufferings of Christ abound in us, so our consolation also aboundeth by Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:5, what abound in us?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "the sufferings of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What aboundeth by Christ in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "our consolation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 1 are endured?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:6",
        "answer": "the same sufferings which we also suffer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two are for your consolation and salvation in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:6",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be afflicted or whether we be comforted"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And our hope of you is stedfast, knowing, that as ye are partakers of the sufferings, so shall ye be also of the consolation.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:7, of what shall ye be partakers?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "the consolation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is stedfast in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "our hope of you"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did we despair in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:8",
        "answer": "even of life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where were we pressed out of measure in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:8",
        "answer": "in Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:9, what does God do?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:9",
        "answer": "raise the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:9, what did we have in ourselves?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:9",
        "answer": "the sentence of death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:10, from what did God deliver us?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:10",
        "answer": "so great a death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:10, what do we trust that God will do?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:10",
        "answer": "that he will yet deliver us"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:11, what may be given by many on our behalf?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:11",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what were ye helping together in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:11",
        "answer": "by prayer (for us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:12, by what have we had our conversation in the world, and more abundantly to you-ward?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:12",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where have we had our conversation in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:12",
        "answer": "in the world and (more abundantly) to you-ward"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:13, when do I trust ye shall acknowledge the things I write unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:13",
        "answer": "(even) to the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:13, what write we unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:13",
        "answer": "none other things, than what ye read or acknowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:14, what are we?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:14",
        "answer": "your rejoicing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:14, when are ye our rejoicing?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:14",
        "answer": "in the day of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:15, in what was I minded to come unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:15",
        "answer": "in this confidence"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:15, why was I minded to come unto you before?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:15",
        "answer": "that ye might have a second benefit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:16, out of where would I come again unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:16",
        "answer": "out of Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:16, where would I be brought on my way?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:16",
        "answer": "toward Judaea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 1 is true?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:18",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:18, what was not yea and nay?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:18",
        "answer": "our word toward you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:19, who is Jesus Christ?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:19",
        "answer": "the Son of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What three preached Jesus Christ among you in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:19",
        "answer": "(me) Paul and Silvanus and Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:20, unto what are all the promises of God yea and Amen in him?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:20",
        "answer": "unto the glory of God (by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are all the promises of God in him in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:20",
        "answer": "yea and Amen, (unto the glory of God by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where has God stablished us with you in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath anointed us in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Now he which stablisheth us with you in Christ.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "and hath anointed us, is God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:22, what hath God given us?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "the earnest of the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: sealed",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "Who hath also sealed us, and given the earnest of the Spirit in our hearts."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:22, where hath God given the earnest of the Spirit?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "in our hearts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath sealed us in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "God (v. 21)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 1:23.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "Moreover I call God for a record upon my soul, that to spare you I came not as yet unto Corinth."
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom do I call for a record in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:23, unto where did I come not as yet?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "unto Corinth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:24, how do ye stand?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "by faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Not for that we have dominion over your faith, but are helpers of your joy: for by faith ye stand.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of what are we helpers in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "of your joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:1, how would I not come again to you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:1",
        "answer": "in heaviness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 2 did I determine with myself?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:1",
        "answer": "(this) that I would not come again to you in heaviness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:2, what do I make you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:2",
        "answer": "sorry"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:3, what is the joy of you all?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "my joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And I wrote this same unto you, lest, when I came, I should have sorrow.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "from them of whom I ought to rejoice; having confidence in you all, that my joy is the joy of you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:3, what should I have from them of whom I ought to rejoice?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "sorrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, why did I write unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "that ye might know the love which I have more abundantly unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, with what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "with many tears"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, out of what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "out of much affliction and anguish of heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: tears",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "For out of much affliction and anguish of heart I wrote unto you with many tears; not that ye should be grieved, but that ye might know the love which I have more abundantly unto you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, how do I have love unto you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "more abundantly"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 2 have any caused?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:5",
        "answer": "grief"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:5, what may I not do?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:5",
        "answer": "overcharge you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:6, to whom is this punishment sufficient?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:6",
        "answer": "to such a man"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was inflicted of many in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:6",
        "answer": "this punishment"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:7, how might such a one be swallowed up?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:7",
        "answer": "with overmuch sorrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:7, what two things ought ye to do?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:7",
        "answer": "rather to forgive him, and comfort him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:8, what do I beseech you?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:8",
        "answer": "that ye would confirm your love toward him"
    },
    {
        "question": "What confirm toward him in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:8",
        "answer": "your love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:9, what might I know?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:9",
        "answer": "the proof of you, (whether ye be obedient in all things)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:9, why did I write?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:9",
        "answer": "(For to this end) that I might know the proof of you, (whether ye be obedient in all things)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, for what did I forgive any thing?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "for your sakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, whom do I forgive?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "(To) whom ye forgive any thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, in whose person did I forgive it?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "the person of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who should get an advantage of us in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "Satan"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:11, of what are we not ignorant?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "of his (Satan's) devices"
    },
    {
        "question": "What should Satan get in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "an advantage of us"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Lest Satan should get an advantage of us: for we are not ignorant of his devices.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 2:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:12, of whom was a door opened unto me?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was opened unto me in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "a door"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was a door opened unto me in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "when I came to Troas (to preach Christ's gospel)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 2:12.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "Furthermore, when I came to Troas to preach Christ's gospel, and a door was opened unto me of the Lord,"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:13, why did I have no rest?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "because I found not Titus my brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 2 is my brother?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "From thence where did I go in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "into Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"I had no rest in my spirit, because I found not Titus.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "my brother: but taking my leave of them, I went from thence into Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who always causeth us to triumph in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: triumph",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "Now thanks be unto God, which always causeth us to triumph in Christ, and maketh manifest the savour of his knowledge by us in every place."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:14, where does God make manifest the savour of his knowledge?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "in every place"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:14, what does God make manifest?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "the savour of his knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is sweet in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "(we are) a sweet savour of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:15, in whom are we a sweet savour of Christ?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "in them that are saved, and in them that perish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For we are unto God a sweet savour of Christ, in them that are saved,and in them that perish:",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 2:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:16, unto what are we the savour of death?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 2:16.",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "To the one we are the savour of death unto death; and to the other the savour of life unto life. And who is sufficient for these things?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unto what are we the savour of life in 2 Corinthians 2 to the other?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "life"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:17, in whose sight speak we in Christ?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "in the sight of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For we are not as many, which corrupt the word of God.\"",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "but as of sincerity, but as of God, in the sight of God speak we in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do many corrupt in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "the word of God"
    }
]